(Episode 28)
(الحلقة 28)
(Director Ko Seong Hui)
(المخرج كو سيونغ هوي)
(I'm sorry about earlier, for asking you to call me Mom.)
(أنا آسف عما سبق، لأنني طلبت منك أن تناديني بأمي.)
What's going on?
ماذا يحدث هنا؟
I'm sorry about earlier, for asking you to call me Mom.
أنا آسف عما سبق، لأنني طلبت منك أن تناديني بأمي.
Call her Mom?
هل نسميها أمي؟
Call me that when it feels right to you.
اتصل بي عندما تشعر أن ذلك مناسب لك.
I just want to hear it once before I die.
أريد فقط أن أسمعها مرة واحدة قبل أن أموت.
My daughter.
ابنتي.
"My daughter?"
"ابنتي؟"
Wait. Then...
انتظر. ثم...
That woman was...
كانت تلك المرأة...
My Eun Oh...
ماي يون أوه...
met her birth mother?
قابلت والدتها الحقيقية؟
When? How?
متى؟ كيف؟
A client.
عميل.
Mom, I got a construction project worth 200,000 dollars today.
أمي، لقد حصلت على مشروع بناء بقيمة 200 ألف دولار اليوم.
Don't tell me they've been meeting ever since then.
لا تخبرني أنهم كانوا يجتمعون منذ ذلك الحين.
So Eun Oh wanted to find her birth mother.
لذا أرادت أون أوه العثور على والدتها الحقيقية.
How long has she felt that way?
منذ متى وهي تشعر بهذه الطريقة؟
Was it since what happened with Gang Oh?
هل كان ذلك منذ ما حدث مع جانج أوه؟
What am I going to do?
ماذا سأفعل؟
Mom.
أم.
Mom?
أم؟
(Mom)
(أم)
What's this? She left her phone.
ما هذا؟ لقد تركت هاتفها.
Mom.
أم.
That's strange.
هذا غريب.
Where could she have gone?
أين يمكن أن تكون ذهبت؟
He needed a liver transplant,
كان يحتاج إلى عملية زرع كبد.
but thankfully, we found a donor and scheduled the surgery.
ولكن لحسن الحظ، وجدنا متبرعًا وحددنا موعدًا للعملية الجراحية.
So what are we supposed to do now? There aren't any other donors.
فماذا علينا أن نفعل الآن؟ لا يوجد متبرعون آخرون.
Does that mean he could die?
هل هذا يعني أنه يمكن أن يموت؟
- Hey! - You scared me.
- مهلا! - لقد أخفتني.
Where's Mom? Why are you praying over the stew?
أين أمي؟ لماذا تصلي على الحساء؟
Hasn't Mom come back from the restaurant yet?
ألم ترجع أمي من المطعم بعد؟
She is back.
لقد عادت.
But I think she just stepped out for a bit.
لكن أعتقد أنها خرجت للتو لفترة قصيرة.
She even left her phone.
حتى أنها تركت هاتفها.
Mom.
أم.
- Where have you been? - Oh, hey.
- أين كنت؟ - أوه، مرحبا.
Well, I was making stew and realised we were out of tofu.
حسنًا، كنت أقوم بتحضير الحساء وأدركت أننا نفدنا من التوفو.
I rushed to the market for some, but I forgot my wallet.
هرعت إلى السوق لشراء بعض منها، ولكنني نسيت محفظتي.
So, I guess we're having the stew without tofu today.
لذا، أعتقد أننا سنتناول الحساء بدون التوفو اليوم.
How could you forget the tofu?
كيف يمكنك أن تنسى التوفو؟
- I know, right? - What?
- أعلم، أليس كذلك؟ - ماذا؟
But the tofu's right there.
ولكن التوفو موجود هناك.
So it is.
وهذا هو الحال.
Gosh, how did I not see it when I looked before?
يا إلهي، كيف لم أره عندما نظرت إليه من قبل؟
Mom, how many fingers do you see? Tell me, how many?
ماما، كم إصبع بتشوفي؟ قولي لي، كم؟
Get out of the way.
ابتعد عن الطريق.
I've secured the capital for 52 percent of the shares.
لقد قمت بتأمين رأس المال لـ 52 بالمائة من الأسهم.
As for the remaining shares, I'll acquire 15 percent in year 1,
أما بالنسبة للأسهم المتبقية، فسوف أستحوذ على 15 بالمائة في السنة الأولى،
then 25 percent in year 2,
ثم 25 في المائة في السنة الثانية،
and the final 10 percent in year 3.
والـ 10% الأخيرة في السنة الثالثة.
I propose a phased acquisition.
أقترح الاستحواذ على مراحل.
You'll oversee my progress as an advisor for three years.
ستشرف على تقدمي كمستشار لمدة ثلاث سنوات.
If I fail to deliver on this promise in three years,
إذا فشلت في الوفاء بهذا الوعد خلال ثلاث سنوات،
I will return the company to you.
سأعيد الشركة إليك.
You want me to give up my company for only half the sale price?
هل تريد مني أن أتخلى عن شركتي مقابل نصف سعر البيع فقط؟
In return, you won't watch AP Group, the company you built, go under.
في المقابل، لن تشاهد مجموعة AP، الشركة التي قمت ببنائها، تنهار.
Rumiko intends to absorb and gut AP Group.
تعتزم روميكو استيعاب وتفكيك مجموعة AP.
And for Yeongsin Paper, who knows how they'll corrupt its identity?
وأما بالنسبة لشركة Yeongsin Paper، فمن يدري كيف سيشوهون هويتها؟
I'm sure you're well aware of this, sir.
أنا متأكد من أنك على علم بذلك جيدًا، سيدي.
What's the guarantee you'll preserve the company's integrity?
ما هي الضمانة التي تضمن لك الحفاظ على نزاهة الشركة؟
Because you didn't get into business just for the money.
لأنك لم تدخل مجال الأعمال من أجل المال فقط.
It has to be fun for it not to feel tiring.
يجب أن يكون الأمر ممتعًا حتى لا تشعر بالتعب.
Only then can you dig in persistently.
حينها فقط يمكنك أن تستمر في التعمق.
And that's how you get results. I saw you say that in an interview.
وهكذا تحصل على النتائج. رأيتك تقول ذلك في مقابلة.
- The interview about the orphanage? - That's what we have in common.
- المقابلة عن دار الأيتام؟ - هذا هو القاسم المشترك بيننا.
Because I also find joy in running and growing my company.
لأنني أجد أيضًا متعة في إدارة شركتي وتنميتها.
I hear you've grown your company well.
لقد سمعت أنك قمت بتنمية شركتك بشكل جيد.
Still, don't you think...
ولكن لا تزال تعتقد...
you're biting off more than you can chew?
أنت تعض أكثر مما تستطيع مضغه؟
Because I couldn't bear to miss this opportunity.
لأنني لم أستطع أن أتحمل تفويت هذه الفرصة.
AP Group is the path I want to take anyway.
مجموعة AP هي المسار الذي أريد اتباعه على أي حال.
I started late and had to be faster. But the fast pace made it exciting.
بدأتُ متأخرًا وكان عليّ أن أسرع. لكن الوتيرة السريعة جعلت الأمر مثيرًا.
Why did you discover your passion so late in life?
لماذا اكتشفت شغفك في وقت متأخر من حياتك؟
Oh, did that punk really go see him?
أوه، هل ذهب هذا الشاب لرؤيته حقًا؟
He certainly seemed determined enough.
لقد بدا بالتأكيد مصمماً بما فيه الكفاية.
Yes. I came back from Cheongpo with this idea...
نعم. عدتُ من تشيونغبو بهذه الفكرة...
for a DIY Interior Design Matching App,
لتطبيق مطابقة التصميم الداخلي DIY،
and that's when I found the work I was meant to do. And I loved it.
وهنا وجدتُ العمل الذي كنتُ أطمح إليه، وأحببتُه.
Ditching your own wedding.
التخلي عن حفل الزفاف الخاص بك.
You made quite the mess.
لقد أحدثت فوضى كبيرة.
- It's a choice I wouldn't make now. - And that's all?
- إنه خيار لن أتخذه الآن. - وهذا كل شيء؟
Are you done?
هل انتهيت؟
Yes. I believe I've said all I need to.
نعم، أعتقد أنني قلت كل ما أحتاج إليه.
You've been watching too many soap operas.
لقد شاهدت عددًا كبيرًا جدًا من المسلسلات.
Excuse me?
اعذرني؟
"An orphan who builds an orphanage, not wanting his kids to inherit..."
"يتيم يبني دارًا للأيتام، لا يريد أن يرث أطفاله..."
And you come to me believing that from a 30-year-old interview?
وتأتي إليّ وتصدق ذلك من مقابلة أجريتها قبل 30 عامًا؟
I built this company for 30 years. You think I'm not a ruthless beast?
لقد بنيتُ هذه الشركة لمدة 30 عامًا. هل تعتقد أنني لستُ وحشًا قاسيًا؟
How could you expect to find the naive, passionate man I was?
كيف يمكنك أن تتوقع أن تجد الرجل الساذج والعاطفي الذي كنت عليه؟
You waltz in with a magazine scrap you read when you were 26...
ترقص مع قصاصة من مجلة قرأتها عندما كان عمرك 26 عامًا...
and shove it in my face? Did you think I was some pushover?
وحطها في وجهي؟ هل ظننتني ضعيفًا؟
- Mr. Chairman, I... - Business is about money.
- السيد الرئيس، أنا... - الأعمال التجارية تتعلق بالمال.
Give up 48 percent and wait 3 years? Would you do that in my shoes?
هل ستتخلى عن ٤٨٪ وتنتظر ٣ سنوات؟ هل كنت لتفعل ذلك لو كنت مكاني؟
Cut the emotional appeal.
قطع النداء العاطفي.
I see.
أرى.
So, you've changed.
إذن لقد تغيرت.
I believed that once a person's values are set,
اعتقدت أنه بمجرد تحديد قيم الشخص،
they stick to them for life.
إنهم يلتزمون بها مدى الحياة.
And that just proves...
وهذا يثبت فقط...
- you're naive. - No.
- أنت ساذج. - لا.
Why don't you just admit that you're the one who's changed?
لماذا لا تعترف بأنك أنت الذي تغير؟
Good luck selling AP Group.
حظا سعيدا في بيع مجموعة AP.
In ten years, you'll see a company a lot like AP. When you do,
خلال عشر سنوات، سترى شركة تشبه AP إلى حد كبير. عندما تفعل ذلك،
take a look at the CEO's name.
إلق نظرة على اسم الرئيس التنفيذي.
He's completely changed.
لقد تغير تماما.
Whatever. The whole AP Group makes me sick.
مهما يكن. مجموعة AP بأكملها تجعلني أشعر بالغثيان.
Gosh, what a waste of energy. I can't believe I listened to Dad.
يا إلهي، يا له من إهدار للطاقة! لا أصدق أنني استمعت لأبي.
Darn it!
لعنة عليك!
I advised my disrespectful son, whether he took it or not.
لقد نصحت ابني الذي لا يحترمني، سواء أخذ بها أم لا.
I can't be the one to lose face.
لا أستطيع أن أكون الشخص الذي يفقد ماء وجهه.
If I fail the practical exam, he'll look down on me even more.
إذا فشلت في الامتحان العملي، فإنه سوف ينظر إلي بازدراء أكثر.
Is that Ji Hyuk?
هل هذا جي هيوك؟
I'm home.
أنا الوطن.
- Ji Hyuk. - Oh, you're back?
- جي هيوك. - أوه، لقد عدت؟
Ji Hyuk...
جي هيوك...
Hey, it's no big deal. It's not like the company failed.
مهلا، الأمر ليس مهمًا. لم تفشل الشركة.
I just crashed.
لقد تحطمت للتو.
But you didn't go to work and slept for two days straight.
ولكنك لم تذهب إلى العمل ونمت لمدة يومين متتاليين.
Of course, we were worried.
بالطبع كنا قلقين.
Ji Hyuk, are you sure nothing's wrong at the company?
جي هيوك، هل أنت متأكد من عدم وجود أي خطأ في الشركة؟
Ji Hyuk, if something's wrong, you have to tell us.
جي هيوك، إذا كان هناك شيء خاطئ، عليك أن تخبرنا.
It's awful for us when we're kept in the dark.
إنه أمر فظيع بالنسبة لنا عندما نبقى في الظلام.
Guys, I'm telling you, it's nothing. I ran on fumes and crashed.
يا شباب، أقول لكم، لا شيء. لقد نفدت سيارتي وتعرضت لحادث.
I was trying to catch up on sleep without anyone knowing,
كنت أحاول تعويض نومي دون أن يعلم أحد،
but Dad had to make a fuss.
لكن كان على الأب أن يثير ضجة.
You're sure nothing's wrong?
هل أنت متأكد من عدم وجود أي خطأ؟
Mom, look at my face.
أمي أنظري إلى وجهي.
You're like a mind reader, Mom. You always know what I'm thinking.
أنتِ كقارئة أفكار يا أمي. أنتِ دائمًا تعرفين ما أفكر فيه.
All right, he's fine.
حسنا، إنه بخير.
Next time, I'll just say that I'm so tired...
في المرة القادمة، سأقول فقط أنني متعب جدًا...
I'm going to sleep for two days.
سأنام لمدة يومين.
I'm going to head upstairs.
سأذهب إلى الطابق العلوي.
Gosh, that was so embarrassing.
يا إلهي، كان ذلك محرجًا جدًا.
No, it's fine.
لا، إنه بخير.
I did everything I could. That's all that matters.
لقد فعلتُ كل ما بوسعي. هذا كل ما يهم.
So you didn't even have the guts to go, did you?
إذن لم يكن لديك الشجاعة للذهاب، أليس كذلك؟
You're jumping to conclusions again. I actually went.
لقد قفزت إلى الاستنتاجات مرة أخرى. لقد ذهبت بالفعل.
You went to meet him?
هل ذهبت لمقابلته؟
I'm just coming back from my meeting with the chairman.
لقد عدت للتو من اجتماعي مع الرئيس.
And?
و؟
What do you mean, "And?" I got completely shot down.
ماذا تقصد بـ "و"؟ لقد تم إسقاطي بالكامل.
I listened to you, and all I got was humiliation.
لقد استمعت إليك، وكل ما حصلت عليه هو الإذلال.
It was a long shot anyway.
لقد كانت محاولة طويلة على أية حال.
You saw it through to the very end. That's what's important.
لقد شاهدته حتى النهاية. هذا هو المهم.
Right. Of course, you've never run a business,
حسنًا. بالطبع، لم تُدِر أي عمل تجاري من قبل،
so it's easy for you to talk.
لذلك فمن السهل بالنسبة لك التحدث.
Hey! Do you have to taste something to know it's rotten?
مهلا! هل يجب عليك تذوق شيء ما لتعرف أنه فاسد؟
What? I may not have run a business myself,
ماذا؟ ربما لم أكن أدير عملاً بنفسي،
but I know enough business owners to know what's what.
لكنني أعرف عددًا كافيًا من أصحاب الأعمال لأعرف ما هو الأمر.
Fine.
بخير.
But I bet it felt good to get it off your chest, right?
لكنني أراهن أنه كان من الجيد أن أخرجه من صدرك، أليس كذلك؟
I guess so.
اعتقد ذلك.
Then that's all that matters. Good.
إذن هذا كل ما يهم. حسنًا.
What do you mean "all that matters?" I'm not okay with this.
ماذا تقصد بـ "كل ما يهم؟" أنا لست موافقًا على هذا.
Then just try again. Honestly, this kid.
حاول مرة أخرى. صدقني، هذا الطفل.
Come on, Ji Hyuk.
هيا، جي هيوك.
What do you mean you're not okay with it?
ماذا تقصد بأنك لست موافق على ذلك؟
It's all over now.
لقد انتهى كل شيء الآن.
Darn it. I shouldn't have told him that.
يا إلهي، ما كان ينبغي لي أن أخبره بذلك.
Why did he have to listen to me this one time?
لماذا كان عليه أن يستمع إلي هذه المرة؟
Of all the things to listen to...
من بين كل الأشياء التي تستحق الاستماع إليها...
I just made him look like a fool for nothing.
لقد جعلته يبدو وكأنه أحمق من دون سبب.
What do you mean "all that matters?" I'm not okay with this.
ماذا تقصد بـ "كل ما يهم؟" أنا لست موافقًا على هذا.
Ji Hyuk.
جي هيوك.
What is it that you're not okay with?
ما هو الشيء الذي لا يناسبك؟
Right.
يمين.
As of today, Seong Jae is the new Vice President.
اعتبارًا من اليوم، سيونغ جاي هو نائب الرئيس الجديد.
- My goodness. Really? - Yes.
- يا إلهي. حقًا؟ - نعم.
Seong Jae, congratulations.
تهانينا سونغ جاي.
Congratulations!
مبروك!
Thank you. Thanks.
شكرا لك. شكرا.
Wow, you really surprised me, honey.
واو، لقد فاجأتني حقًا، عزيزتي.
You should've given me a heads-up. I would've prepared a party.
كان يجب عليك أن تُخبرني مُسبقًا. كنت سأُحضّر حفلة.
Why make a fuss? It's just the next natural step.
لماذا كل هذا الضجيج؟ إنها مجرد خطوة طبيعية.
"The next natural step?"
"الخطوة الطبيعية التالية؟"
Oh, right.
أوه، صحيح.
What's your schedule like today?
ما هو جدولك اليوم؟
How about the four of us grab lunch to celebrate?
ماذا عن أن نتناول الغداء معًا للاحتفال؟
See? There you go again.
هل رأيت؟ ها أنت ذا مرة أخرى.
The Magnolia Society meeting is today.
اجتماع جمعية ماغنوليا اليوم.
Today's not great for me either.
اليوم ليس جيدا بالنسبة لي أيضا.
- Let's do it after the launch. - Right. I forgot about that.
- لنفعل ذلك بعد الإطلاق. - صحيح. لقد نسيتُ ذلك.
Okay, let's do that.
حسنًا، لنفعل ذلك.
What a relief.
يا له من ارتياح!
I had my heart set on getting some gopchang today.
لقد كنت أرغب بشدة في الحصول على بعض الجوبتشانج اليوم.
You're up 700 grams?
هل زاد وزنك 700 جرام؟
Yes.
نعم.
Mr. Lee has been buying you snacks, hasn't he?
لقد كان السيد لي يشتري لك الوجبات الخفيفة، أليس كذلك؟
How could you gain 700 grams just from eating salads?
كيف يمكنك الحصول على 700 جرام فقط من تناول السلطة؟
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
A few days ago, I was stuck in traffic,
قبل بضعة أيام، كنت عالقًا في حركة المرور،
and there was a vendor selling fish-shaped pastries.
وكان هناك بائع يبيع معجنات على شكل سمكة.
You ate street food?
هل أكلت طعام الشارع؟
No.
لا.
I was starving on my way out of the gym,
كنت جائعًا في طريقي للخروج من صالة الألعاب الرياضية،
so at the bakery downstairs,
لذا في المخبز في الطابق السفلي،
I got a pastry, a cream-filled bun,
حصلت على معجنات، كعكة محشوة بالكريمة،
a canele, and some macarons,
عصا وبعض الماكرونات
and we split them.
وقسمناهم.
Are you out of your mind?
هل أنت خارج عقلك؟
But I stopped immediately, and I've been working out every day.
لكنني توقفت على الفور، وأصبحت أمارس الرياضة كل يوم.
I'm very on edge these days.
أنا متوترة جدًا هذه الأيام.
The last thing I need is you getting on my nerves, Yeong Ra.
آخر شيء أحتاجه هو أن تزعج أعصابي، يونغ را.
A woman's self-discipline should be as natural as breathing.
ينبغي أن يكون الانضباط الذاتي للمرأة طبيعيا مثل التنفس.
I understand.
أفهم.
Because of your father...
بسبب والدك...
Never mind.
لا تهتم.
I'm so dead.
أنا ميتة تماما.
Mom's going to make me weigh myself every day now.
أمي سوف تجعلني أزن نفسي كل يوم الآن.
(Second date with Su Bin)
(الموعد الثاني مع سو بين)
Meet me at 8pm by the parking lot at Yeonji-dong Mart.
قابلني في الساعة 8 مساءً عند موقف السيارات في Yeonji-dong Mart.
Wear something casual.
ارتدي شيئًا غير رسمي.
Something with loose sleeves.
شيء بأكمام فضفاضة.
Something with loose sleeves?
شيء بأكمام فضفاضة؟
Man, where are we even going?
يا رجل، إلى أين نحن ذاهبون؟
Gosh, what a pain. It's a hassle to pick out an outfit.
يا إلهي، يا له من أمرٍ مُرهق! اختيار الملابس مُرهقٌ للغاية.
I'm craving beef gopchang.
أنا مشتاق إلى لحم البقر جوبتشانغ.
Fried rice made with it is so good.
الأرز المقلي المصنوع منه لذيذ جدًا.
No. Starting today, you're back on the salad diet.
لا، ابتداءً من اليوم، ستعود إلى نظامك الغذائي المعتمد على السلطة.
You're right. Mom's going to make me get on the scale twice a week.
أنت على حق. أمي ستجعلني أقيس وزني مرتين في الأسبوع.
- But, hey... - Gosh, seriously!
- لكن، مهلا... - يا إلهي، بجدية!
Stop talking. I can't figure out the plot.
توقف عن الكلام. لا أستطيع فهم القصة.
Never mind.
لا تهتم.
- I can eat it and work out, right? - Just drop it.
- أستطيع أن آكله وأمارس الرياضة، أليس كذلك؟ - فقط اتركه.
Hey, you never know when your mom might show up for a surprise visit.
مهلا، أنت لا تعرف أبدًا متى قد تظهر والدتك في زيارة مفاجئة.
That only happened because we never checked the app after installing it.
لقد حدث هذا فقط لأننا لم نتحقق من التطبيق بعد تثبيته.
Let's start checking it every hour.
فلنبدأ بالتحقق منه كل ساعة.
(Mom's Car, Guri, Yangpyeong)
(سيارة أمي، غوري، يانغبيونغ)
What?
ماذا؟
What? What's wrong?
ماذا؟ ما الخطب؟
What? What is it?
ماذا؟ ما هو؟
Mom has her Magnolia Society meeting today,
أمي لديها اجتماع جمعية ماغنوليا اليوم،
so why is she heading toward Guri?
فلماذا تتجه نحو جوري؟
- Maybe it's in Guri or Yangpyeong. - No way.
- ربما يكون في جوري أو يانغبيونغ. - لا يمكن.
It's a key corporate wives' meeting. It has to be in Gangnam.
إنه اجتماع رئيسي لزوجات مديرات الشركات. لا بد أنه في غانغنام.
I think they even have a regular spot.
أعتقد أن لديهم مكانًا منتظمًا.
Then where could she be going?
إذن إلى أين يمكنها أن تذهب؟
(Mom's Car)
(سيارة أمي)
Seojong-myeon, Seohu-ri?
سيوجونغ-ميون، سيوهو-ري؟
Why is Mom's car all the way out here?
لماذا سيارة أمي موجودة هنا طوال الطريق؟
It's on the move.
إنه في حالة تحرك.
Hey, keep an eye on where it's going for me.
مهلا، راقب إلى أين تتجه الأمور بالنسبة لي.
Why? What are you going to do?
لماذا؟ ماذا ستفعل؟
What?
ماذا؟
I'm just going to check the comments.
سأقوم فقط بالتحقق من التعليقات.
Hey, stop reading comments and work on your webtoon.
مهلا، توقف عن قراءة التعليقات واعمل على الويبتون الخاص بك.
Okay. Just five more minutes, then I'll start drawing.
حسناً، خمس دقائق فقط، ثم سأبدأ الرسم.
Everyone's dying to know what happens in the next episode.
الجميع يموتون شوقًا لمعرفة ما سيحدث في الحلقة القادمة.
Finally...
أخيراً...
Okay, just breathe normally. Hold still.
حسنًا، تنفس بشكل طبيعي. ابقَ ساكنًا.
Okay, good.
حسنا، جيد.
The liver scan reading is higher than last time.
قراءة فحص الكبد أعلى من المرة السابقة.
(Jin Seung Ki, Professor of Surgery)
(جين سونغ كي، أستاذ الجراحة)
This is concerning. The waiting list is still very long.
هذا أمرٌ مُقلق. قائمة الانتظار لا تزال طويلةً جدًا.
Excuse me, Doctor.
عذرا يا دكتور.
If we find a compatible donor,
إذا وجدنا متبرعًا متوافقًا،
my Woo Jin can get the surgery right away, can't he?
هل يستطيع وو جين إجراء العملية الجراحية على الفور؟
Yes, but there's still a long waiting list.
نعم، ولكن لا تزال هناك قائمة انتظار طويلة.
He has a younger sibling.
لديه شقيق أصغر منه.
His sister is coming to get tested for compatibility.
أخته قادمة لإجراء اختبار التوافق.
Besides yourself,
بالإضافة إلى نفسك،
I thought you said no one else in your family could be tested.
اعتقدت أنك قلت أنه لا يمكن اختبار أي شخص آخر في عائلتك.
I found the daughter I lost long ago.
لقد وجدت ابنتي التي فقدتها منذ زمن طويل.
She'll be coming in for the test.
إنها ستأتي لإجراء الاختبار.
These are the results of a checkup she had recently. Take a look.
هذه نتائج فحصها الطبي الذي أجرته مؤخرًا. ألقِ نظرة.
Even for siblings,
حتى بالنسبة للأشقاء،
there's only a 25 percent chance of a perfect match.
هناك فرصة 25 في المائة فقط للحصول على تطابق مثالي.
So please don't get your hopes up.
لذا من فضلك لا ترفع سقف آمالك.
No.
لا.
I have a good feeling about this.
لدي شعور جيد حول هذا الموضوع.
But please don't let Woo Jin know about any of this.
ولكن من فضلك لا تدع وو جين يعرف أي شيء من هذا.
I want to tell him after the surgery is over and he's fully recovered.
أريد أن أخبره بعد أن تنتهي العملية الجراحية ويتعافى بشكل كامل.
Of course.
بالطبع.
Getting his hopes up prematurely would only be more disappointing.
إن رفع آماله قبل الأوان لن يؤدي إلا إلى المزيد من خيبة الأمل.
If his condition keeps getting worse like this,
إذا استمرت حالته في التدهور على هذا النحو،
what if he develops hepatic encephalopathy?
ماذا لو أصيب بمرض اعتلال الدماغ الكبدي؟
The stress is killing me.
الضغط يقتلني.
Are you all right?
هل انت بخير؟
I was worried about you.
لقد كنت قلقا عليك.
(Director Ko)
(مديري)
(Are you all right? I was worried about you.)
(هل أنت بخير؟ لقد كنت قلقة عليك.)
Could you come over today?
هل بإمكانك المجيء اليوم؟
I have nowhere to grieve, and I can't even allow myself to.
ليس لدي مكان للحزن، ولا أستطيع حتى أن أسمح لنفسي بذلك.
I've waited all day, and with so much to look into,
لقد انتظرت طوال اليوم، ومع وجود الكثير من الأشياء التي يجب النظر إليها،
I'm completely stuck here.
أنا عالق هنا تماما.
She has nowhere to grieve,
ليس لديها مكان للحزن،
and she can't even allow herself to grieve.
وهي لا تستطيع حتى أن تسمح لنفسها بالحزن.
Okay. I'll head over right after work.
حسنًا، سأذهب إلى هناك بعد العمل مباشرةً.
(Okay. I'll head over right after work.)
(حسنًا، سأتوجه إلى هناك بعد العمل مباشرةً.)
Wait, are you really going through with this?
انتظر، هل أنت حقا تقوم بهذا؟
- So you're going for the final bid? - That's the plan.
- إذن أنت ذاهب إلى العرض النهائي؟ - هذه هي الخطة.
But, Mr. Lee.
ولكن السيد لي.
You said your meeting with AP's chairman didn't go well.
قلت أن اجتماعك مع رئيس AP لم يكن جيدًا.
- That's right. - Why are you still going for it?
- هذا صحيح. - لماذا لا تزال تسعى إلى ذلك؟
Because the bidding isn't over yet.
لأن المزايدة لم تنتهي بعد
Once you start climbing, you must reach the top, even if you crawl.
بمجرد أن تبدأ في التسلق، يجب عليك الوصول إلى القمة، حتى لو كنت تزحف.
Only then will you have no regrets.
حينها فقط لن يكون لديك أي ندم.
There you are, standing in that same spot again.
ها أنت ذا، تقف في نفس المكان مرة أخرى.
Yes.
نعم.
About yesterday...
عن الأمس...
I heard your meeting with AP's chairman didn't go well.
سمعت أن اجتماعك مع رئيس AP لم يكن جيدًا.
Have you eaten?
هل أكلت؟
And if I said no, would you have a meal with me?
وإذا قلت لا هل تتناول وجبة طعام معي؟
Don't ask if you're not going to join me.
لا تسأل إذا كنت لن تنضم إلي.
Then why are you here?
إذن لماذا أنت هنا؟
I came to give you this.
لقد جئت لأعطيك هذا.
I had some the other day. They're really good.
لقد تناولتُ بعضًا منها بالأمس. إنها لذيذة جدًا.
You like hotteok, right?
أنت تحب هوتيوك، أليس كذلك؟
Why are you going to this trouble for me?
لماذا تفعل هذا من أجلي؟
What, you really don't know?
ماذا، أنت حقا لا تعرف؟
I'm showing you I care because you're the woman I like.
أنا أظهر لك أنني أهتم لأنك المرأة التي أحبها.
I thought we were done talking about this.
اعتقدت أننا انتهينا من الحديث عن هذا.
I would never let someone like that into my life.
لن اسمح لشخص مثله بالدخول إلى حياتي أبدًا.
Do you think feelings just end that easily?
هل تعتقد أن المشاعر تنتهي بهذه السهولة؟
If it were that easy,
لو كان الأمر بهذه السهولة،
then why did you insist on a reason back then?
إذن لماذا أصريت على وجود سبب في ذلك الوقت؟
Why was it so important to you?
لماذا كان ذلك مهمًا جدًا بالنسبة لك؟
For someone who knows how it feels, you're being so cold, and it hurts.
بالنسبة لشخص يعرف كيف يشعر، فإنك تشعر بالبرد الشديد، وهذا يؤلم.
Those feelings will fade in time.
هذه المشاعر سوف تتلاشى مع مرور الوقت.
I have plans, so I should get going.
لدي خطط، لذلك يجب أن أبدأ.
You see, I...
كما ترى، أنا...
I'm going to see the final bid through.
سأرى العرض النهائي حتى النهاية.
You're going for it, even though you know you'll lose?
هل ستذهب إلى هذا الأمر، على الرغم من أنك تعلم أنك ستخسر؟
Yes.
نعم.
If you pull it off, I'll buy you a meal.
إذا نجحت في ذلك، سأشتري لك وجبة طعام.
That's a promise.
هذا وعد.
I just said it to show you I'm rooting for you.
لقد قلت ذلك فقط لأظهر لك أنني أشجعك.
Are you really getting your hopes up?
هل حقا لديك آمالك العالية؟
I don't know.
لا أعرف.
Anyway, I'll keep trying with AP until it works out,
على أية حال، سأستمر في المحاولة مع AP حتى ينجح الأمر،
and I'm going to do the same with you.
وسأفعل نفس الشيء معك.
You just do whatever you want.
فقط افعل ما تريد.
Bye.
الوداع.
Director Ko.
مديري.
Eun Oh.
يون أوه.
They said it was okay to go in.
قالوا أنه من المقبول الدخول.
Of course. It's you, after all.
بالطبع. أنت، بعد كل شيء.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
You look exhausted.
أنت تبدو مرهقًا.
I couldn't sleep at all last night.
لم أستطع النوم إطلاقا الليلة الماضية.
I'm just so upset.
أنا مستاء للغاية.
I can only imagine.
يمكنني أن أتصور.
And it's not just that.
وليس هذا فقط.
It's you.
إنه أنت.
Me?
أنا؟
We've only just found each other, and now this happens.
لقد وجدنا بعضنا البعض للتو، والآن يحدث هذا.
Now that I've found you, I want to see you every day,
الآن بعد أن وجدتك، أريد رؤيتك كل يوم،
but I can't even smile or be truly happy about it.
ولكنني لا أستطيع حتى أن أبتسم أو أن أكون سعيدًا حقًا بهذا الأمر.
That's understandable, given your situation.
وهذا أمر مفهوم، بالنظر إلى وضعك.
So what's going to happen now?
فماذا سيحدث الآن؟
I'll have to throw money at the problem.
سوف أضطر إلى إلقاء المال على المشكلة.
I hear there are people who can arrange that sort of thing.
سمعت أن هناك أشخاصًا يمكنهم ترتيب هذا النوع من الأشياء.
For a liver transplant, you must get a compatibility test,
لإجراء عملية زرع الكبد، يجب عليك إجراء اختبار التوافق،
but the odds... If 100 people get tested,
لكن الاحتمالات... إذا تم اختبار 100 شخص،
the chance of a match is only 1 to 3 percent.
فرصة التطابق هي 1 إلى 3 في المئة فقط.
Even among siblings, it's only a 25 percent chance.
حتى بين الأشقاء، فإن الفرصة لا تتجاوز 25 في المائة.
Eun Oh.
يون أوه.
Would you consider...
هل ستفكر في...
No. Never mind. It's nothing, Eun Oh.
لا، لا بأس. لا شيء يا يون أوه.
Why? What is it? Please, just tell me.
لماذا؟ ما هو؟ أرجوك، فقط أخبرني.
It's just...
إنه فقط...
Would you be willing to at least get tested?
هل ترغب في إجراء الاختبار على الأقل؟
What?
ماذا؟
My husband doesn't know about any of this.
زوجي لا يعرف أي شيء من هذا.
He didn't want to be a burden on his stepfather,
لم يكن يريد أن يكون عبئا على زوج أمه،
so he wanted to hide his illness.
فأراد إخفاء مرضه.
You've been dealing with this alone?
هل كنت تتعامل مع هذا الأمر بمفردك؟
At the end of the day,
وفي نهاية اليوم،
he's not his child.
إنه ليس طفله.
I'll...
سوف...
I'll get tested.
سأجري الاختبار.
You'd do that for me?
هل ستفعل ذلك من أجلي؟
I just feel like I have to do this so I won't have any regrets.
أشعر فقط أنني يجب أن أفعل هذا حتى لا أشعر بأي ندم.
Whatever it takes, I have to try everything I can.
مهما كان الأمر، يجب أن أحاول كل ما بوسعي.
I'm his mother, after all.
أنا أمه، بعد كل شيء.
I can get tested first thing tomorrow.
يمكنني إجراء الاختبار أول شيء غدًا.
(Damga Charcoal Grill)
(شواية دامجا الفحمية)
Oh, dear.
يا عزيزي.
Why would she try to find them?
لماذا تحاول العثور عليهم؟
- Mom, what did you say? - What?
- ماما، ماذا قلتِ؟ - ماذا؟
Oh, nothing. Just thinking out loud.
لا شيء. فقط أفكر بصوت عالٍ.
I thought she was abandoned. Why would she want to find them?
ظننتُ أنها مهجورة. لماذا تُريد العثور عليهم؟
No. There must have been another reason.
لا، لابد أن يكون هناك سبب آخر.
Did her birth mother show up? That's it.
هل ظهرت أمها الحقيقية؟ هذا كل شيء.
She must have shown up, so Eun Oh didn't have a choice.
لا بد أنها ظهرت، لذلك لم يكن أمام أون أوه خيار.
But she was abandoned with no record,
لكنها تركت دون أي سجل،
so we could adopt her.
حتى نتمكن من تبنيها.
How could her mother have found her?
كيف استطاعت أمها أن تجدها؟
Right, Eun Oh must have registered her DNA.
حسنًا، يبدو أن أون أوه قد سجل حمضها النووي.
Gang Oh.
عصابة أوه.
Now,
الآن،
you really don't hold anything against your sister?
هل حقا لا تحمل أي شيء ضد أختك؟
What?
ماذا؟
Do you really see her as just your sister?
هل تعتبرها حقا مجرد أختك؟
Yes, of course.
نعم بالطبع.
Then why did you act that way back then?
إذن لماذا تصرفت بهذه الطريقة في ذلك الوقت؟
When you found out she was adopted, you were just so cruel to her,
عندما علمت أنها متبناة، كنت قاسيًا جدًا معها،
and you were so angry.
وكنت غاضبا جدا.
Mom, I already told you.
أمي لقد أخبرتك بالفعل.
I just felt so hopeless about my future back then.
لقد شعرت بخيبة أمل كبيرة بشأن مستقبلي في ذلك الوقت.
And it wasn't that I hated her. I was just hung up on blood ties.
ولم يكن الأمر أنني أكرهها، بل كنت مهووسًا بروابط الدم فقط.
Blood ties?
روابط الدم؟
Back then, I wanted to get rich fast and hated working here.
في ذلك الوقت، كنت أرغب في الثراء بسرعة وكرهت العمل هنا.
So everything just came down to money for me.
بالنسبة لي، كل شيء كان يعتمد على المال.
"Blood is thicker than water." I was brainwashed by those words.
"الدم أثخن من الماء". لقد غسلت دماغي بهذه الكلمات.
"Blood is thicker than water?"
"الدم أكثر سمكا من الماء؟"
Mom, when someone just snaps, they can act like a total psycho.
أمي، عندما يفقد شخص ما أعصابه فجأة، فإنه يمكن أن يتصرف وكأنه شخص مختل عقليًا تمامًا.
After what happened with Gang Oh,
بعد ما حدث مع جانج أوه،
I wonder if you felt differently too, Eun Oh.
أتساءل عما إذا كنت تشعر بشكل مختلف أيضًا، إيون أوه.
- Great work, everyone. - You too.
- عمل رائع، الجميع. - وأنت أيضًا.
(Shoealls)
(أحذية)
Where's she taking me that she told me to wear loose sleeves?
أين تأخذني وهي تطلب مني أن أرتدي أكمامًا فضفاضة؟
Now, I'm really curious.
الآن، أنا فضولي حقًا.
This is cute.
هذا لطيف.
You know, you actually look prettier without makeup.
هل تعلمين أنك تبدين أجمل بدون مكياج؟
No, I take that back. You look better with makeup.
لا، أتراجع عن كلامي. تبدين أجمل بالمكياج.
Make sure you wear makeup when you see your boyfriend.
تأكدي من وضع الماكياج عند رؤية صديقك.
He said I was prettier without makeup.
قال أنني أجمل بدون مكياج.
And he told me to wear makeup for my boyfriend?
وقال لي أن أضع مكياج لصديقي؟
You're home.
أنت في المنزل.
What are you doing home so early?
ماذا تفعلين في المنزل مبكرا؟
I was just feeling a little tired today.
لقد كنت أشعر بالتعب قليلاً اليوم.
Did you have fun at your Magnolia Society meeting?
هل استمتعت بوقتك في اجتماع جمعية ماغنوليا؟
Do you think I go to those meetings to have fun?
هل تعتقد أنني أذهب إلى هذه الاجتماعات من أجل المتعة؟
You need a lesson on your choice of words.
تحتاج إلى درس في اختيار الكلمات.
You should ask, "Did you have a pleasant time?"
ينبغي عليك أن تسأل، "هل قضيت وقتًا ممتعًا؟"
That's the more refined way to ask.
هذه هي الطريقة الأكثر دقة للسؤال.
Did you have a pleasant time at your Magnolia Society meeting?
هل قضيت وقتًا ممتعًا في اجتماع جمعية ماغنوليا؟
We exchanged some useful information.
لقد تبادلنا بعض المعلومات المفيدة.
Mom's lying.
أمي تكذب
I'll see you at dinner.
سوف أراك على العشاء.
Okay.
تمام.
I'm so curious.
أنا فضولي جدًا.
Why would Mom have gone to Yangpyeong?
لماذا ذهبت أمي إلى يانغبيونغ؟
I have to find out what's going on.
يجب أن أعرف ماذا يحدث.
Just park the car. It's right here.
فقط اركن السيارة. إنها هنا.
Seriously? The place she picked is just a cafe?
بجد؟ المكان اللي اختارته مجرد مقهى؟
Well, that's anticlimactic, Su Bin.
حسنًا، هذا أمر مخيب للآمال، سو بين.
Hey!
يا!
- Hey, did you eat yet? - Yes, I ate at home.
-مرحبًا، هل أكلت بعد؟ -نعم، لقد أكلت في المنزل.
At home?
في البيت؟
I thought you wanted to meet at 8pm because you were busy.
اعتقدت أنك تريد أن نلتقي في الساعة الثامنة مساءً لأنك كنت مشغولاً.
The launch is keeping you busy. You've eaten too, right?
الإطلاق يُبقيك مشغولاً. لقد أكلتَ أيضاً، أليس كذلك؟
Yes, of course. The team and I ordered in.
نعم، بالطبع. أنا والفريق طلبنا الطعام.
Wait, so she suggested 8pm just for me?
انتظر، هل اقترحت الساعة الثامنة مساءً من أجلي فقط؟
Why the look? If we meet at 8pm, we get 4 hours until midnight.
لماذا هذا المظهر؟ إذا التقينا الساعة الثامنة مساءً، لدينا أربع ساعات حتى منتصف الليل.
It's nothing.
لا شئ.
It's just that tea at 8pm seemed lame. That's why.
لكن شرب الشاي الساعة الثامنة مساءً بدا غير مناسب. لهذا السبب.
Oh, really? Well, that's not what we're doing.
أوه، حقًا؟ حسنًا، هذا ليس ما نفعله.
Come on!
تعال!
Hey. What is this place?
مهلا، ما هذا المكان؟
A knitting shop?
محل حياكة؟
Today's activity is knitting scarves to exchange with each other.
نشاط اليوم هو حياكة الأوشحة لتبادلها مع بعضنا البعض.
You want me to knit?
هل تريدني أن أحيك؟
- Come on, Su Bin. This is too much. - Hey.
- هيا يا سو بين، هذا كثير جدًا. - هيا.
Didn't we agree that I'd be the one choosing where we go?
ألم نتفق على أن أكون أنا من يختار المكان الذي نذهب إليه؟
I know, but it's still a bit much, you know?
أعرف ذلك، ولكن لا يزال الأمر مبالغًا فيه بعض الشيء، هل تعلم؟
You might change your mind once you try it.
ربما تغير رأيك بمجرد تجربته.
We're not allowed to go home until we finish these.
لن يُسمح لنا بالعودة إلى المنزل حتى ننتهي من هذه الأمور.
Let's each pick the colour we want. I want...
ليختار كلٌّ منا اللون الذي يريده. أنا أريد...
yellow.
أصفر.
For me...
لي...
I'm good with anything.
أنا جيد في أي شيء.
Anything's fine? Then I'll pick one out for you.
هل هناك أي شيء جيد؟ إذن سأختار لك واحدًا.
I think you'd look good in any of them, but...
أعتقد أنك ستبدو جيدًا في أي منها، ولكن...
What? Is this one too bright?
ماذا؟ هل هذا ساطع جدًا؟
What's your personal colour?
ما هو لونك الشخصي؟
I don't know. I've never done that test.
لا أعلم، لم أقم بهذا الاختبار من قبل.
- You said you liked yellow, right? - Yes. You put it in like this,
قلتَ إنك تحب الأصفر، صحيح؟ - نعم. وضعته هكذا،
then loop it around.
ثم قم بتدويرها حول بعضها.
- Okay, hold on. In like this... - Loop.
- حسنًا، انتظر. هكذا... - حلقة.
And loop.
و حلقة.
Su Bin. How about I just buy you a scarf?
سو بين، ما رأيك أن أشتري لك وشاحًا؟
Look. Do you think the people here can't afford to buy a scarf,
انظر، هل تعتقد أن الناس هنا لا يستطيعون شراء وشاح؟
so that's why they're knitting?
لذلك فإنهم يحيكون؟
I know, right? Why is everyone here doing this?
أعرف، صحيح؟ لماذا يفعل الجميع هذا هنا؟
Just try it. You'll get it once you're finished.
جرّبه فقط، وستحصل عليه فور انتهائك منه.
Why? What, because you're some...
لماذا؟ ماذا، لأنك...
third-generation heir, you can't do this sort of thing?
الوريث من الجيل الثالث، لا يمكنك أن تفعل هذا النوع من الأشياء؟
What are you talking about? That's ridiculous.
عن ماذا تتحدث؟ هذا سخيف.
Show me again.
أرني مرة أخرى.
If I put my mind to it, I can do anything.
إذا وضعت في ذهني ذلك، أستطيع أن أفعل أي شيء.
It'll be easier if we're looking from the same angle.
سيكون الأمر أسهل إذا نظرنا من نفس الزاوية.
Look.
ينظر.
See? Like this.
هل رأيت؟ مثل هذا.
He has nice hands, too. His fingers are so long.
يديه جميلتان أيضًا. أصابعه طويلة جدًا.
And his eyelashes are long, too.
ورموشه طويلة أيضاً.
So that's what he looks like when he smiles without realising it.
وهذا ما يبدو عليه عندما يبتسم دون أن يدرك ذلك.
What?
ماذا؟
Su Bin, look at this.
سو بين، انظر إلى هذا.
What? Oh, okay.
ماذا؟ أوه، حسنًا.
You dropped a stitch.
لقد أسقطت غرزة.
In and loop.
في حلقة.
Yes, right here. This part! How did you do this?
نعم، هنا تمامًا. هذا الجزء! كيف فعلتَ هذا؟
I'm all done.
لقد انتهيت من كل شيء.
- Hey! Wait, stay just like that! - What?
- هيه! انتظر، ابق هكذا! - ماذا؟
Okay.
تمام.
Wow, you're a real natural at this.
واو، أنت طبيعي جدًا في هذا.
- Hey, this is kind of fun... - Excuse me, we'll be closing soon.
- مهلا، هذا ممتع نوعًا ما... - معذرة، سوف نغلق قريبًا.
Okay.
تمام.
Wow, it's that late already?
واو، لقد تأخر الوقت بالفعل؟
Why haven't you gotten much done? What were you doing?
لماذا لم تُنجز الكثير؟ ماذا كنت تفعل؟
You're just a really fast knitter.
أنت مجرد حائك سريع جدًا.
I'll finish this and give it to you on our next date.
سأنهي هذا وأعطيه لك في موعدنا القادم.
Didn't you say you couldn't go home until you finished?
ألم تقل أنك لن تستطيع العودة إلى المنزل حتى تنتهي؟
So, does that mean I don't have to go home?
فهل هذا يعني أنني لست بحاجة للعودة إلى المنزل؟
Let's go home.
دعنا نذهب إلى المنزل.
That's pretty cool.
هذا رائع جدًا.
Time flies when you do this. It's more fun than I thought.
يمرّ الوقت سريعًا عندما تفعل هذا. إنه أكثر متعة مما كنت أعتقد.
- It's great for clearing your head. - Right? It's great for de-stressing.
- إنه رائع لتصفية الذهن. - صحيح؟ إنه رائع لتخفيف التوتر.
So is that why you wanted to come here today?
فهل هذا هو السبب الذي جعلك ترغب في المجيء إلى هنا اليوم؟
Yes. You've had a lot on your mind lately.
نعم، كان هناك الكثير في ذهنك مؤخرًا.
When something big is coming up, your thoughts get tangled, right?
عندما يحدث شيء كبير، تتشابك أفكارك، أليس كذلك؟
Thanks. You really helped me clear my head.
شكراً، لقد ساعدتني حقاً على تصفية ذهني.
Really? Yes! Today's date was a success!
حقاً؟ نعم! كان موعد اليوم ناجحاً!
Here. An early Christmas present.
هنا. هدية عيد الميلاد المبكرة.
An early Christmas present?
هدية عيد الميلاد المبكرة؟
So he's saying he doesn't want to see me on Christmas.
فهو يقول أنه لا يريد رؤيتي في عيد الميلاد.
Did you have fun too?
هل استمتعت أنت أيضاً؟
Yes, totally.
نعم، تماما.
Me too. Come on. I'll take you home today.
أنا أيضًا. هيا. سآخذك إلى المنزل اليوم.
Really?
حقًا؟
That's two down.
هذا اثنان لأسفل.
One more to go.
واحد آخر للذهاب.
What a lame date. So lame.
يا له من موعدٍ تافه! تافهٌ جدًا.
I mean...
أعني...
How can I see her as a woman if I don't even get to look at her?
كيف يمكنني أن أراها كامرأة إذا لم أتمكن حتى من النظر إليها؟
Knitting to clear my head? What kind of date is that?
حياكة لتصفية ذهني؟ ما هذا الموعد؟
Unbelievable.
لا يصدق.
Gosh, whatever.
يا إلهي، لا يهم.
I only have to go out with her...
كل ما علي هو أن أخرج معها...
one more time, and then I'm done.
مرة أخرى، ثم انتهيت.
Mom, I'm sorry.
أمي، أنا آسف.
I absolutely have to be at the construction site today.
يجب علي أن أكون في موقع البناء اليوم.
I know. You told me last night.
أنا أعلم. لقد أخبرتني الليلة الماضية.
Good luck.
حظ سعيد.
Don't worry, I'll be fine. It'd be overkill if you came anyway.
لا تقلق، سأكون بخير. سيكون الأمر مبالغًا فيه لو أتيت على أي حال.
- Okay, I'll get going then. - Okay.
- حسنًا، سأذهب إذن. - حسنًا.
She's probably going to see her birth mother.
من المحتمل أن ترى والدتها الحقيقية.
It's not like Eun Oh to miss something this important.
ليس من عادات إيون أوه أن يفوت شيئًا مهمًا كهذا.
(Cheong Ah University Hospital)
(مستشفى جامعة تشيونغ آه)
When you get to the hospital, you'll meet with a doctor first.
عندما تصل إلى المستشفى، سوف تقابل طبيبًا أولاً.
They'll ask for your consent and things like that.
سيطلبون موافقتك وأشياء من هذا القبيل.
(Damga)
(ختم)
I'm so nervous.
أنا متوترة جدًا.
Hey, I'm supposed to be the nervous one.
مهلا، من المفترض أن أكون الشخص المتوتر.
You started this, and you're making me more nervous.
لقد بدأت هذا الأمر، وأنت تجعلني أكثر توتراً.
I wish Eun Oh were here.
أتمنى أن يكون أون أوه هنا.
I know, Mom. Even though my sister is tiny,
أعرف يا أمي، مع أن أختي صغيرة،
she seemed so big in Dad's role. So bold and fearless.
she seemed so big in Dad's role. So bold and fearless.
That's enough.
هذا يكفي.
Yes, you can come in now.
Yes, you can come in now.
Okay.
تمام.
(Damga Corp, R and D Center)
(Damga Corp, R and D Center)
Looking at these ingredients, this must be your secret recipe.
Looking at these ingredients, this must be your secret recipe.
Yes. I marinate it once with this,
Yes. I marinate it once with this,
and a second time with this special marinade.
and a second time with this special marinade.
The natural enzymes must've deepened the meat's flavour.
The natural enzymes must've deepened the meat's flavour.
It was exceptionally tender before. I was curious what the secret was.
It was exceptionally tender before. I was curious what the secret was.
If this dish gets chosen,
If this dish gets chosen,
I'll reveal the secret ingredient ratios then.
I'll reveal the secret ingredient ratios then.
It's a healthy method, so customers can enjoy it worry-free.
It's a healthy method, so customers can enjoy it worry-free.
Exactly. These days, food must be more than delicious.
Exactly. These days, food must be more than delicious.
It needs to leave a lasting impression on customers.
It needs to leave a lasting impression on customers.
It seemed a shame to keep it all to ourselves,
It seemed a shame to keep it all to ourselves,
so I'm the one who called HQ to ask if we could sell it.
so I'm the one who called HQ to ask if we could sell it.
We're glad you did.
We're glad you did.
Ms. Ji Eun Oh's test is going well.
Ms. Ji Eun Oh's test is going well.
From her liver size to her blood vessels...
From her liver size to her blood vessels...
She's already a suitable match, anyway.
She's already a suitable match, anyway.
Take a deep breath.
Take a deep breath.
Now, hold it.
Now, hold it.
You're taking this test of your own free will, correct?
You're taking this test of your own free will, correct?
A living donor liver transplant is the best option, you see.
A living donor liver transplant is the best option, you see.
Well, just because you're siblings doesn't guarantee a match,
Well, just because you're siblings doesn't guarantee a match,
so don't get your hopes up too high.
so don't get your hopes up too high.
- Why isn't Eun Oh here today? - Well...
- Why isn't Eun Oh here today? - Well...
It's a personal matter, so it's not really my place to say.
It's a personal matter, so it's not really my place to say.
Su Jeong.
Su Jeong.
I really can't. You should ask Eun Oh yourself.
I really can't. You should ask Eun Oh yourself.
She's never missed a day of school. That's why I'm asking.
She's never missed a day of school. That's why I'm asking.
All right, fine.
All right, fine.
It's so obvious he likes Eun Oh.
It's so obvious he likes Eun Oh.
(Wow, I can't believe this outfit is 68 years old.)
(Wow, I can't believe this outfit is 68 years old.)
(Bini, gorgeous colours. I love the vibe.)
(Bini, gorgeous colours. I love the vibe.)
(- I'd totally buy this outfit. - Grandma looks just like a model.)
(- I'd totally buy this outfit. - Grandma looks just like a model.)
(She's so elegant.)
(She's so elegant.)
The more I read this, the more fascinating it gets.
The more I read this, the more fascinating it gets.
Tell me about it.
Tell me about it.
I was embarrassed at first,
I was embarrassed at first,
but here I am reading these with you.
but here I am reading these with you.
Wait a second. What's this?
Wait a second. What's this?
What does this say?
What does this say?
Hello. I'm the vice president of the Senior Model Association.
Hello. I'm the vice president of the Senior Model Association.
I think the woman in your video would make a great senior model.
I think the woman in your video would make a great senior model.
If she's interested, please have her contact us at this number.
If she's interested, please have her contact us at this number.
What is this saying?
What is this saying?
Oh, my! They're asking you to be a senior model, Ok Rye!
Oh, my! They're asking you to be a senior model, Ok Rye!
Oh, my goodness. No way.
Oh, my goodness. No way.
Oh, dear.
Oh, dear.
(Jamun Medical Devices)
(Jamun Medical Devices)
Welcome.
مرحباً.
Could you take care of this customer for a moment?
Could you take care of this customer for a moment?
Yes, I'll give it a try.
Yes, I'll give it a try.
Welcome.
مرحباً.
Well, my mother-in-law mentioned this,
Well, my mother-in-law mentioned this,
and I was thinking of getting one for my father.
and I was thinking of getting one for my father.
In that case, why don't you try this first?
In that case, why don't you try this first?
Here, please lie down.
Here, please lie down.
Come on, Dad. Lie down.
Come on, Dad. Lie down.
This is an eco-friendly product.
This is an eco-friendly product.
It's nice and warm, isn't it?
It's nice and warm, isn't it?
Oh, my. That's nice and warm.
Oh, my. That's nice and warm.
What do you call it? It feels like it's improving my circulation.
What do you call it? It feels like it's improving my circulation.
My mother-in-law gets a lot of use out of hers.
My mother-in-law gets a lot of use out of hers.
Dad, what do you think?
Dad, what do you think?
Do you like it?
Do you like it?
If you keep using it, it'll help with your aches and pains.
If you keep using it, it'll help with your aches and pains.
Let's get it then, Dad.
Let's get it then, Dad.
I'll buy it for you.
I'll buy it for you.
Depression is no big deal. It happens when you get old.
Depression is no big deal. It happens when you get old.
At my age,
At my age,
nothing ever happens.
nothing ever happens.
So you just naturally start to feel down.
لذا تبدأ بشكل طبيعي بالشعور بالاكتئاب.
Come on, Da Jeong.
هيا، دا جونغ.
Why do you care what Gyeong Hun thinks?
لماذا تهتم بما يعتقده كيونغ هون؟
You just saw a daughter taking such good care of her father.
لقد رأيت للتو ابنة تعتني جيدًا بأبيها.
I'm supposed to leave mine alone while he's on antidepressants?
هل من المفترض أن أتركه بمفرده أثناء تناوله مضادات الاكتئاب؟
Gyeong Hun.
جيونج هون.
It's me, your sister.
أنا أختك.
I'm texting because we need to talk about something important.
أرسل لك رسالة نصية لأننا بحاجة إلى التحدث عن شيء مهم.
You know Dad's turning 90 soon.
أنت تعلم أن أبي سيبلغ التسعين قريبًا.
And he's been living alone for ten years now.
وقد عاش وحيدًا لمدة عشر سنوات الآن.
(Gyeong Hun)
(كيونغ هون)
You know it's not possible for me to take him in,
أنت تعلم أنه ليس من الممكن بالنسبة لي أن آخذه معي،
so to make sure Dad isn't lonely in his final years,
ولكي أتأكد من أن أبي لن يشعر بالوحدة في سنواته الأخيرة،
do you think you could have him move in with you?
هل تعتقد أنه بإمكانك جعله ينتقل للعيش معك؟
Give me that.
أعطني ذلك.
Wait, what is this?
انتظر، ما هذا؟
What are you talking about?
ماذا تتحدث عنه؟
Did you really plan to send your father...
هل كنت تخطط حقا لإرسال والدك...
to live with your brother without even talking to me first?
أن تعيش مع أخيك دون أن تتحدث معي أولًا؟
What else am I supposed to do?
ماذا علي أن أفعل غير ذلك؟
I can't stand seeing my dad live all by himself anymore.
لا أستطيع أن أتحمل رؤية والدي يعيش بمفرده بعد الآن.
Dad...
أب...
He's been on antidepressants.
لقد كان يتناول مضادات الاكتئاب.
Why didn't you tell me that?
لماذا لم تخبرني بذلك؟
You should have told me this. Come on.
كان يجب عليك أن تخبرني بهذا. هيا.
Is this because I'm not making enough money right now?
هل هذا لأنني لا أكسب ما يكفي من المال في الوقت الحالي؟
Da Jeong.
دا جونغ.
Did my words go in one ear and out the other?
هل دخلت كلماتي من أذن وخرجت من الأخرى؟
I told you he could come live with us.
لقد قلت لك أنه يمكنه أن يأتي ليعيش معنا.
What? Mother, you said he could live with us?
ماذا؟ أمي، قلتِ إنه يستطيع العيش معنا؟
Yes. Su Bin and I can share a room, and he can have mine.
نعم، أنا وسو بين نستطيع مشاركة الغرفة، وهو يستطيع الحصول على غرفتي.
No, I couldn't ask you to do that.
لا، لا أستطيع أن أطلب منك القيام بذلك.
Why not? Of course, we can do it.
لماذا لا؟ بالطبع، يمكننا فعل ذلك.
We can just kick out either Ji Wan or Ji Hyuk.
يمكننا فقط أن نطرد إما جي وان أو جي هيوك.
Mother offered to let your father move in, right?
لقد عرضت والدتك على والدك أن ينتقل للعيش معك، أليس كذلك؟
But still, there's Gyeong Hun.
ولكن لا يزال هناك جيونج هون.
You wrote that text to your brother,
لقد كتبت هذا النص لأخيك،
but you couldn't hit send, could you?
لكنك لم تتمكن من الضغط على زر الإرسال، أليس كذلك؟
You were afraid he'd say no, weren't you?
كنت خائفة من أن يقول لا، أليس كذلك؟
Mother.
الأم.
Are you really sure you'd be okay with my father living here?
هل أنت متأكد حقًا من أنك ستكون بخير مع عيش والدي هنا؟
And you're really okay with this?
وهل أنت بخير حقا مع هذا؟
- Of course! - Of course! Honestly...
- بالطبع! - بالطبع! بصراحة...
- Honey, it's Gyeong Hun. - Answer it.
- عزيزتي، أنا جيونج هون. - أجيبي عليه.
Hello? Gyeong Hun?
مرحباً؟ كيونغ هون؟
Hey. Sorry it took me so long to call back.
مرحباً، آسف لأني تأخرت كثيراً في الاتصال.
Yes. Isn't it like 1am in Seattle now?
نعم. أليست الساعة الآن الواحدة صباحًا في سياتل؟
We moved today. We just finished unpacking.
انتقلنا اليوم. انتهينا للتو من تفريغ الأمتعة.
- You moved? - Yes, into a four-bedroom place.
- انتقلت؟ - نعم، إلى مكان به أربع غرف نوم.
So Dad can come and live with us.
حتى يتمكن الأب من المجيء والعيش معنا.
You want Dad to live with you?
هل تريد أن يعيش والدك معك؟
Apparently, my sister-in-law suggested it first.
يبدو أن أخت زوجي هي من اقترحت ذلك أولاً.
Her mother passed away at the beginning of the year.
توفيت والدتها في بداية العام.
So she told him he'd regret it for the rest of his life...
فأخبرته أنه سوف يندم على ذلك طيلة حياته...
if he didn't ask our father to come live with them.
إذا لم يطلب من والدنا أن يأتي ليعيش معهم.
Still, that means leaving the country.
ومع ذلك، فهذا يعني مغادرة البلاد.
Do you think your father will be happy with that?
هل تعتقد أن والدك سيكون سعيدًا بذلك؟
- He'll be thrilled. - Da Jeong!
- سوف يكون سعيدًا. - دا جونغ!
- Sang Cheol! - Father.
- سانغ تشول! - أبي.
- My goodness. - Oh, Ok Rye.
- يا إلهي. - أوه، حسنًا راي.
My Gyeong Hun asked me to come.
لقد طلب مني جيونج هون أن آتي.
He wants me to live with him.
يريدني أن أعيش معه.
- "Ok Rye?" - "Ok Rye?"
- "حسنًا يا راي؟" - "حسنًا يا راي؟"
Wait, how did they become friends just by being neighbours?
انتظر، كيف أصبحوا أصدقاء فقط من خلال كونهم جيرانًا؟
You heard him. He said he had no friends left.
لقد سمعته. قال إنه لم يعد لديه أصدقاء.
Wow, I've never seen your father look so happy.
واو، لم أرى والدك سعيدًا هكذا من قبل.
He must have been so lonely.
لابد أنه كان وحيدًا جدًا.
I'm sorry, honey. Okay?
أنا آسف يا عزيزتي. حسنًا؟
What about Mother once my dad leaves?
ماذا عن أمي عندما يتركني أبي؟
She'll feel so empty.
ستشعر بالفراغ الشديد.
Kim Da Jeong.
كيم دا جونغ.
Stay with me for a long time.
ابقى معي لفترة طويلة.
For a long time? How long?
منذ زمن طويل؟ إلى متى؟
At this rate, we probably have at least another 20 years together.
بالمعدل الحالي، من المحتمل أن نبقى معًا لمدة 20 عامًا أخرى على الأقل.
No, maybe 30, looking at our parents.
لا، ربما 30، بالنظر إلى والدينا.
Thirty years?
ثلاثين سنة؟
Oh, you're right.
أوه، أنت على حق.
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
I won't burden you with being the sole provider until then.
لن أثقل عليك بكوني المزود الوحيد حتى ذلك الحين.
I'll be right there with you.
سأكون هناك معك.
Don't be ridiculous.
لا تكن سخيفا.
I'll be the one providing for you until the day I die. Honestly...
سأكون من سيتكفل بك حتى مماتي. بصراحة...
This is exactly why I married you.
وهذا هو السبب بالضبط الذي جعلني اتزوجك.
Mom, Gang Oh.
أمي، جانج أوه.
- So how was it today? - It felt like it was a shoo-in.
- إذن كيف كان الأمر اليوم؟ - بدا الأمر كما لو كان الفوز حليفنا.
I think Mom's galbi is going to be a new menu item.
أعتقد أن غالبي أمي سيكون عنصرًا جديدًا في القائمة.
Wow, really?
واو، حقا؟
My gosh. You really worked hard, Mom.
يا إلهي، لقد اجتهدتِ حقًا يا أمي.
Goodness.
الخير.
Hey, I'm exhausted.
مهلا، أنا مرهق.
I'm heading to bed.
أنا متجه إلى السرير.
Gang Oh.
عصابة أوه.
Did something happen to upset Mom today?
هل حدث شيء أزعج أمي اليوم؟
No, I don't think so. She was proud of the great response.
لا، لا أعتقد ذلك. كانت فخورة بالاستجابة الرائعة.
So is she just really exhausted then?
إذن، هل هي مرهقة حقًا؟
Of course, she is. Our mom is a huge introvert,
بالطبع، هي كذلك. أمنا انطوائية للغاية،
and she had to do a demo at corporate HQ.
وكان عليها أن تقوم بعرض توضيحي في المقر الرئيسي للشركة.
Yes, that makes sense.
نعم، هذا منطقي.
That little brat.
هذا الطفل الصغير.
I can't believe she didn't say anything.
لا أستطيع أن أصدق أنها لم تقل شيئاً.
My gosh.
يا إلهي.
(Bid Envelope)
(ظرف العطاء)
- Your submission is complete. - Okay.
- تم إكمال إرسال طلبك. - حسنًا.
(Bidder: Lee Ji Hyuk)
(المُزايد: لي جي هيوك)
- Shall we go? - Yes.
- هل نذهب؟ - نعم.
Wait, Mr. Lee, you're here for the final bidding?
انتظر، السيد لي، هل أنت هنا للمزايدة النهائية؟
Yes.
نعم.
For crying out loud.
من أجل الصراخ بصوت عال.
This is ridiculous.
هذا سخيف.
Thank you for seeing this through with me.
شكرا لك على رؤية هذا معي.
Regardless of the outcome, we've learned a lot from this too.
وبغض النظر عن النتيجة، فقد تعلمنا الكثير من هذا أيضًا.
Your fighting spirit and tenacity...
روحك القتالية ومثابرتك...
It's something we never would have dreamed of.
إنه شيء لم نكن لنحلم به أبدًا.
If that's how it seemed, it's all thanks to my father.
إذا كان الأمر يبدو هكذا، فالفضل كله يعود لأبي.
- Pardon? - He told me to go for it.
- عفواً؟ - لقد طلب مني أن أذهب إليه.
Whether it worked out or not,
سواء نجح الأمر أم لا،
I figured it'd be better than regretting not trying.
اعتقدت أن هذا سيكون أفضل من الندم على عدم المحاولة.
I see.
أرى.
You really left it all on the table. So how do you feel?
لقد تركت كل شيء على الطاولة. فكيف تشعر؟
Relieved.
مرتاح.
I know the feeling. I feel relieved myself.
أعرف هذا الشعور. أشعر بالارتياح.
What?
ماذا؟
(Yoon Tae Sik Vice President, AP Group)
(يون تاي سيك نائب الرئيس لمجموعة AP)
Hello, this is Lee Ji Hyuk.
مرحبًا، أنا لي جي هيوك.
Mr. Lee. The chairman wants to see you now.
السيد لي، الرئيس يريد رؤيتك الآن.
- Pardon? - I'll text you the contract needs.
- عفواً؟ - سأرسل لك رسالة تحتوي على احتياجات العقد.
Prepare them and come.
جهزهم وتعالوا.
What do you mean by that?
ماذا تقصد بذلك؟
He's handing the company to you, Mr. Lee.
إنه يسلم الشركة إليك، السيد لي.
What?
ماذا؟
(Exclusive Negotiation Agreement)
(اتفاقية التفاوض الحصرية)
What are you staring at so dreamily? Weren't you expecting this at all?
ما الذي تحدق فيه بنظرة حالمة؟ ألم تتوقع هذا أصلًا؟
You're a very convincing actor, Mr. Chairman.
أنت ممثل مقنع للغاية، السيد الرئيس.
You were just acting that day, weren't you?
لقد كنت تمثل فقط في ذلك اليوم، أليس كذلك؟
I made my decision the day you came to see me.
لقد اتخذت قراري في اليوم الذي أتيت فيه لرؤيتي.
I want to hand my company over to someone who will grow it well.
أريد أن أسلم شركتي لشخص قادر على نموها بشكل جيد.
What would I do with all that money from the sale at my age, anyway?
ماذا سأفعل بكل هذه الأموال من البيع في عمري هذا على أي حال؟
But...
لكن...
I needed to be sure.
كنت بحاجة للتأكد.
Whether you had just ambition, or the grit to back it up too.
سواء كان لديك مجرد طموح، أو الشجاعة لدعمه أيضًا.
The kind of man who finishes what he starts...
الرجل الذي ينهي ما يبدأه...
would make it to the final bid, so I waited to see.
سأصل إلى العرض النهائي، لذلك انتظرت لأرى.
Thank you for believing in me.
شكرا لك على ثقتك بي.
I won't let you down.
لن أخذلك .
Please take good care of this company.
من فضلك اعتني بهذه الشركة جيدًا.
This is our company logo.
هذا هو شعار شركتنا.
I had this made once I made up my mind.
لقد قمت بصنع هذا بمجرد أن اتخذت قراري.
To help me let go of the company.
لمساعدتي في ترك الشركة.
I wanted to give it to the new owner as a gift.
أردت أن أعطيها للمالك الجديد كهدية.
Now,
الآن،
it's not my company anymore.
إنها لم تعد شركتي بعد الآن.
This is gorgeous.
هذا رائع.
The height of the sink...
ارتفاع الحوض...
and the furniture too.
والأثاث أيضا.
Everything is exactly how I wanted it.
كل شيء هو بالضبط كما أردته.
Really?
حقًا؟
Eun Oh!
يون أوه!
Hello.
مرحبًا.
These kitchen cabinets. They're from AP Kitchen, right?
خزائن المطبخ هذه. إنها من AP Kitchen، أليس كذلك؟
Yes.
نعم.
Ma'am, I'll personally handle the after-sales service for these.
سيدتي، سأتولى بنفسي خدمة ما بعد البيع لهذه المنتجات.
Pardon me?
اعذرني؟
Because AP Kitchen's head office handles all after-sales service.
لأن المكتب الرئيسي لشركة AP Kitchen يتولى كافة خدمات ما بعد البيع.
Hey, don't get ahead of yourself. We only submitted the bid today.
لا تستعجل، لقد قدمنا ​​العرض اليوم فقط.
No, the results are in. It's official. We're acquiring them.
لا، النتائج وصلت. إنها رسمية. نحن نستلمها.
I even signed the contract with the chairman.
حتى أنني وقعت العقد مع الرئيس.
Really? But how? All in one day?
حقاً؟ ولكن كيف؟ كل ذلك في يوم واحد؟
Ms. Ji Eun Oh.
السيدة جي إيون أوه.
Shouldn't you get back to work? The client is still here.
ألا يجب عليك العودة إلى العمل؟ العميل لا يزال هنا.
Make sure everything suits the client's lifestyle.
تأكد من أن كل شيء يناسب نمط حياة العميل.
Do a final check. The details are everything.
قم بإجراء فحص نهائي. التفاصيل هي كل شيء.
- Ma'am, please look over here. - Okay.
- سيدتي، من فضلك انظري إلى هنا. - حسنًا.
Are you happy with the interior design?
هل أنت سعيد بالتصميم الداخلي؟
Of course.
بالطبع.
Ms. Ji was so meticulous with every detail.
كانت السيدة جي دقيقة للغاية في كل التفاصيل.
My husband especially loves the tea room.
زوجي يحب غرفة الشاي بشكل خاص.
You mean the wooden floor in there?
هل تقصد الأرضية الخشبية الموجودة هناك؟
Ms. Ji treated that floor with natural oils herself.
قامت السيدة جي بمعالجة تلك الأرضية بالزيوت الطبيعية بنفسها.
You didn't have to say that.
لم يكن عليك أن تقول ذلك.
They should appreciate all your hard work.
ينبغي عليهم أن يقدروا كل عملك الجاد.
Okay, I get it. Just head back to the office.
حسناً، فهمتُ. فقط عُد إلى المكتب.
Everyone must be waiting for you.
لا بد أن الجميع في انتظارك.
We're going together. You're our turnkey team leader.
سنذهب معًا. أنت قائد فريقنا الجاهز.
I already asked Su Jeong to get everything set up.
لقد طلبت بالفعل من Su Jeong إعداد كل شيء.
Thank you for all your hard work. You must visit after I move in.
شكراً جزيلاً على جهودكم. سأزوركم بعد انتقالي.
It was a pleasure working on it.
لقد كان من دواعي سروري العمل عليه.
- Take your time and look around. - I will.
- خذ وقتك وانظر حولك. - سأفعل.
I could just look at it all day. You two should get going.
أستطيع أن أشاهده طوال اليوم. يجب عليكما أن تنطلقا.
Are you tired?
هل انت متعب؟
- Here you go. - Thanks.
- تفضل. - شكرا.
Ji Eun Oh, you owe me dinner.
جي إيون أوه، أنت تدين لي بالعشاء.
I only said that because I thought you'd lose.
قلت ذلك فقط لأنني اعتقدت أنك ستخسر.
I know. But I won.
انا أعلم. ولكنني فزت.
A promise is a promise.
الوعد هو الوعد.
Tell me about it on the way.
أخبرني عن ذلك في الطريق.
About how you found your birth parents.
حول كيفية العثور على والديك البيولوجيين.
Not my parents. Just my birth mother.
ليس والديّ، فقط أمي الحقيقية.
She said my father passed away.
قالت أن والدي توفي.
I see.
أرى.
What about your birth mother?
ماذا عن والدتك الحقيقية؟
What's she like?
كيف هي؟
How did she say she lost you?
كيف قالت أنها فقدتك؟
The thing is...
الشئ هو...
She's someone I already knew.
إنها شخص أعرفه بالفعل.
You already knew her?
هل كنت تعرفها بالفعل؟
You know that client I had for the art space job?
هل تعرف ذلك العميل الذي كان لدي للعمل في مجال المساحة الفنية؟
Yes, I remember her. And?
نعم أتذكرها. و؟
It was her.
لقد كانت هي.
The one who gave birth to me.
الذي ولدتني.
What?
ماذا؟
No, how is that even possible?
لا، كيف يكون ذلك ممكنا؟
(Laparoscopic Liver Transplant 7-day stay, 2-week recovery)
(زراعة الكبد بالمنظار تستغرق 7 أيام، وفترة نقاهة لمدة أسبوعين)
A trip to Europe with a friend.
رحلة إلى أوروبا مع صديق.
But work could make that difficult.
ولكن العمل قد يجعل ذلك صعبا.
But three weeks is too long for just the Milan Expo.
لكن ثلاثة أسابيع مدة طويلة جدًا لمعرض ميلانو فقط.
(Ms. Shin)
(السيدة شين)
Yes, Ms. Shin.
نعم، السيدة شين.
Find a short interior design course at a New York fashion school.
ابحث عن دورة قصيرة في التصميم الداخلي في إحدى مدارس الأزياء في نيويورك.
Actually, Paris would be fine too. Anywhere in Europe will do.
في الواقع، باريس ستكون مناسبة أيضًا. أي مكان في أوروبا مناسب.
Yeong Ra.
يونغ را.
Yeong Ra, come on. It's time to go home.
يونغ را، هيا. حان وقت العودة إلى المنزل.
Why are they suddenly holding hands and running?
لماذا فجأة يمسكون بأيدي بعضهم ويركضون؟
What's going on here?
ماذا يحدث هنا؟
Remember when Mom almost caught us? Running away with you was so fun...
هل تتذكرون عندما كادت أمي أن تقبض علينا؟ كان الهروب معكم ممتعًا جدًا...
that I turned it into an episode.
أنني حولتها إلى حلقة.
You thought that was fun?
هل ظننت أن هذا كان ممتعا؟
Yes. My heart was pounding,
نعم، كان قلبي ينبض بقوة.
but it was such a thrill.
ولكن كان الأمر مثيرا للغاية.
It was a rush, you know?
لقد كان اندفاعًا، هل تعلم؟
You've really got guts.
لقد حصلت على الشجاعة حقا.
Right, my mom.
حسنًا، أمي.
(Mom's Car)
(سيارة أمي)
Hey, does this have a feature...
مرحبًا، هل هذه ميزة...
that sends an alert when my mom's car starts moving?
الذي يرسل تنبيهًا عندما تبدأ سيارة أمي في التحرك؟
I don't think so. I already set it to give you an hourly reminder.
لا أعتقد ذلك. لقد ضبطته بالفعل ليُذكرك كل ساعة.
That's not what I mean.
هذا ليس ما أقصده.
I think I might have to follow my mom.
أعتقد أنني قد أضطر إلى اتباع أمي.
Follow Director Ko?
اتبع مديري؟
Why?
لماذا؟
Something's fishy about Yangpyeong.
هناك شيء مريب في يانغبيونغ.
What if she's having an affair?
ماذا لو كانت لها علاقة غرامية؟
Come on. There's no way.
هيا، لا يوجد طريقة.
That's why we have to find out.
ولهذا السبب علينا أن نكتشف ذلك.
No, I have to be sure.
لا، يجب أن أكون متأكدًا.
If only for my dad's sake.
ولو من أجل والدي فقط.
But how are you going to know when to follow her?
ولكن كيف ستعرف متى يجب عليك متابعتها؟
I'll just follow her using the GPS tracker.
سأتبعها باستخدام جهاز تعقب GPS.
On a day when her route seems strange?
في يوم يبدو فيه طريقها غريبًا؟
Good point. You're pretty smart.
نقطة جيدة. أنت ذكي جدًا.
Thank you, everyone. To AP Group!
شكرًا جزيلاً للجميع. لمجموعة AP!
- To AP Group! - To AP Group!
- إلى مجموعة AP! - إلى مجموعة AP!
- Thank you. - Thank you.
- شكرا لك. - شكرا لك.
- Well done. - Mr. Lee Ji Hyuk.
- أحسنت. - السيد لي جي هيوك.
Seriously, congratulations.
بجدية، مبروك.
Man, you're incredible. Seriously.
أنت رائع يا رجل. بجد.
I think so, too.
أعتقد ذلك أيضًا.
There's that obnoxious Lee Ji Hyuk again.
هناك ذلك لي جي هيوك المزعج مرة أخرى.
Since you're talking so casually, I'll ask you like your boss.
بما أنك تتحدث بطريقة غير رسمية، فسأطلب منك مثل رئيسك.
Why did you miss work yesterday?
لماذا تغيبت عن العمل أمس؟
- I bet we're getting a raise. - Mr. Jo.
- أراهن أننا سنحصل على زيادة. - السيد جو.
Mr. Lee Ji Hyuk.
السيد لي جي هيوك.
Seriously, stop giving everyone a heart attack.
بجدية، توقف عن إعطاء الجميع نوبة قلبية.
Sung Guk looked like he was about to lose his mind.
لقد بدا سونغ جوك وكأنه على وشك أن يفقد عقله.
But he keeps things exciting, doesn't he?
لكنّه يبقي الأمور مثيرة، أليس كذلك؟
Here, Mr. Lee.
هنا السيد لي.
It's not time to get drunk yet. We have lots of work tomorrow.
لم يحن وقت السُكر بعد. لدينا الكثير من العمل غدًا.
Of course.
بالطبع.
It didn't even take as long as I thought it would.
لم يستغرق الأمر وقتًا طويلاً كما كنت أعتقد.
But what if you're a match?
ولكن ماذا لو كنت متوافقا؟
The odds are low.
الاحتمالات منخفضة.
They said there was only a 25 percent chance...
قالوا أن هناك فرصة 25 في المئة فقط
of a perfect match.
من مباراة مثالية.
I just got tested. That's all.
لقد أجريتُ الاختبار للتو. هذا كل شيء.
But what will you do if you're in that 25 percent?
ولكن ماذا ستفعل إذا كنت ضمن تلك النسبة 25 بالمائة؟
As if.
كأنه.
Su Jeong, you know more about this than I do, don't you?
سو جونغ، أنت تعرف عن هذا الأمر أكثر مني، أليس كذلك؟
When will you meet the twin brother you mentioned earlier?
متى سوف تلتقي بالأخ التوأم الذي ذكرته سابقًا؟
They say twins have a special connection.
يقولون أن التوائم لديهم اتصال خاص.
You never felt anything?
هل شعرت بأي شيء أبدًا؟
Su Jeong.
سو جونغ.
Oh, okay.
أوه، حسنا.
You must be really happy to finally meet him.
لا بد أنك سعيد حقًا بلقائه أخيرًا.
So? When are you going to meet him?
إذن؟ متى ستقابله؟
He's not feeling well, so I can't see him for a while.
إنه لا يشعر بأنه على ما يرام، لذلك لا أستطيع رؤيته لفترة من الوقت.
What? If he's not well, you should see him even sooner.
ماذا؟ إذا لم يكن بخير، عليك رؤيته في أقرب وقت.
Just how sick is he?
ما مدى مرضه؟
Is it terminal?
هل هو طرفي؟
It's nothing like that.
إنه ليس مثل ذلك على الإطلاق.
Then what is it?
ثم ما هو؟
What kind of illness keeps you from meeting someone?
ما هو نوع المرض الذي يمنعك من مقابلة شخص ما؟
There's no such illness in the world.
لا يوجد مثل هذا المرض في العالم.
There is. Just drop it.
هناك. فقط أسقطه.
No, I can't just drop it.
لا، لا أستطيع أن أسقطه.
None of this makes any sense.
لا يوجد أي معنى لكل هذا.
His liver is in really bad shape,
كبده في حالة سيئة للغاية،
so he's waiting for a liver transplant.
لذلك فهو ينتظر عملية زرع الكبد.
What?
ماذا؟
Don't tell me...
لا تخبرني...
Did they ask you to take the compatibility test?
هل طلبوا منك إجراء اختبار التوافق؟
Yesterday...
أمس...
Is that why you missed work?
هل هذا هو السبب الذي جعلك تتغيب عن العمل؟
That's what it was.
هذا ما كان عليه الأمر.
- No, it's not like that... - Come here.
- لا، ليس الأمر كذلك... - تعال هنا.
Have a seat over here.
خذ مقعدا هنا.
What are you doing? Everyone's watching.
ماذا تفعل؟ الجميع يراقب.
Tell me.
أخبرني.
How much do you really know about your biological mother?
ما مقدار ما تعرفه حقًا عن والدتك البيولوجية؟
This whole "coincidence" thing...
هذا الشيء كله "صدفة" ...
Have you actually verified it?
هل تأكدت من ذلك فعليا؟
What are you trying to say?
ماذا تحاول أن تقول؟
It's too much of a coincidence. Don't you think it's strange?
إنها مصادفةٌ مُبالغٌ فيها. ألا تعتقد أنها غريبة؟
You just happened to meet her as a client.
لقد صادف أنك التقيت بها كعميل.
And it turns out she's your birth mother.
وتبين أنها أمك الحقيقية.
And now, your brother needs a liver transplant.
والآن أخوك يحتاج إلى عملية زرع كبد.
All the pieces...
كل القطع...
fit together too perfectly, don't you think?
يتناسبان معًا بشكل مثالي، ألا تعتقد ذلك؟
(Our Golden Days)
(أيامنا الذهبية)
- Vice President Park Seong Jae. - Get in there, quickly.
- نائب الرئيس بارك سيونج جاي. - ادخل إلى هناك بسرعة.
Don't worry. I won't tell them I was with you.
لا تقلق، لن أخبرهم أنني كنت معك.
I must have missed something.
لا بد أنني فاتني شيء ما.
Do you really think Director Ko is having an affair?
هل تعتقد حقا أن المخرج كو لديه علاقة غرامية؟
I just feel like I need to know what my mom is doing...
أشعر أنني بحاجة لمعرفة ما تفعله أمي...
and what she's up to.
وماذا تفعل؟
Doesn't it seem strange to you? This whole liver transplant thing...
ألا يبدو الأمر غريبًا بالنسبة لك؟ عملية زراعة الكبد هذه...
is really bothering me. In life, things don't just...
يزعجني حقًا. في الحياة، الأمور لا تسير على ما يرام فحسب...
fall into place so perfectly like this.
تقع في مكانها بشكل مثالي مثل هذا.
Did I ask you to work for me? Do you think I'd just exploit you?
هل طلبتُ منك العمل معي؟ أتظن أنني سأستغلك؟
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
I'll give it all up.
سأتخلى عن كل شيء.